before we move on to the next stage
which would be dis patch let's do a
issue quiz so in this quiz we have our
instruction queue we have a rat we have
a register file we have a reservation
stations these two instructions are
already reservation stations there are
two left to issue and these are the
values of the register file of the Rat
Etc so your task is to issue these two
instructions or at least issue those
that can be issued at this time you
don't need to consider when these
extractions are going to finish so just
issue whatever can be issued in the next
several Cycles assuming that these are
just not going to leave from here
anytime soon